<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MapCalibration android app on MapCalibration - easy satnav for paper maps</title>
    <link>https://maciek252.github.io/MapCalibration/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MapCalibration android app on MapCalibration - easy satnav for paper maps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://maciek252.github.io/MapCalibration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>https://maciek252.github.io/MapCalibration/docs/docsen/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maciek252.github.io/MapCalibration/docs/docsen/overview/</guid>
      <description>MapCalibration The MapCalibration app&#39;s aim is to assist satnav-based navigation for maps without GPS coordinates. The main idea is to calibrate the map by setting reference markers on a satellite photo map, in locations easy to identify on both maps. Then, the app computes the map scale. From now on, an user can identify locations on the calibrated map by measuring distances from reference markers.
Types of markers In detail, there are the following types of markers (colors correspond to colors of respective markers):
Reference markers   reference marker - specified by the marker on the photo map or gps coordinates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://maciek252.github.io/MapCalibration/docs/docsen/configure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:30:08 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maciek252.github.io/MapCalibration/docs/docsen/configure/</guid>
      <description>Syntax highlighting and menus can be configured via &lt;code&gt;config.toml&lt;/code&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Example</title>
      <link>https://maciek252.github.io/MapCalibration/docs/docsen/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maciek252.github.io/MapCalibration/docs/docsen/example/</guid>
      <description>Example In the example we will show how a location in the terrain can be found on the basis of its identification on the map we are given. Below we present the steps to be performed:
 The map we use  Assume that we are given the following map (either electronic or printed on the paper).
The units we use for measuging distances are relevant only for the scale (proportion of distance on the map and distance in the terrain). When we do not care about the scale, we can use any units (pixels, centimeters, milimeters, inches, etc).
The reference point  We choose the first reference point at the intersection (a location easy to identify both on the map and in the sat photo).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>